Uncle, give me a ticket.
Where do you want to go, son?   Don't know.
Then what is the ticket for?
Give me the ticket first, I will think about it on the way.
Yes.  [laughter]
Son, should I get the stuff picked up?
No uncle, I will pick it up myself.
Being so young?
Yes, mom has said that you should learn to bear the burden of life yourself.
[laughter]
Son, would you like some tea?
No, uncle.
Why?
Mom makes tea at home.
So?
Then why should I drink your tea and get scolded at home
?
[laughter]
Son, why are you wandering around here alone?   I am
looking for mom.
What does mommy look like?
When she gets angry, she is scarier than the police.
[laughter]
Uncle, where is my seat?   I do
n't know son.
No uncle.
Where is the ticket?   I don't know that either.
Then how are you sitting here?
Uncle, on the strength of confidence.
Show the ticket.
Uncle, I don't have a ticket.
Then how did you board the train?
Uncle, I have not come from the door or the window.
[laughter]
Son, what are you going to be when you grow up?
Very rich.
Will you earn money?
No, grandma.
Then how are you rich?   I will
go to my mother and ask her to give me the money.
[laughter]
Son, did you bother anyone on the train
?
No mom.
Sure?
Yes.
Just made some people laugh.  [laughter]
Son, why are you sad?   I
make videos with so much hard work.  Then
people laugh but don't follow or subscribe.
Please do it.